A Guide to the Tom Buckley Collection on Virginia Political Campaign Memorabilia, 1963-2009 (bulk 1969-1983)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 1: Pamphlets, 1963-2009
  - Charles L. Waddell (State Senate), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Earl F. Wagner (Commonwealth Attorney), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Marvin H. Wagner (Delegate), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - George Wallace (President), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - James K. Walters (Treasurer-Fairfax County Democratic Committee), 1975 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - John W. Warner (U.S. Senate), Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Mark R. Warner (Governor, U.S. Senate), 2001-2008 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - John B. Watkins, IV (State Senate), 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Patricia Watt (Chair-Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Vivian Watts (Chair-Board of Supervisors, Delegate), Undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Karl Weickhardt (Justice of Peace, Delegate), Undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Robert L. Weinberg (House of Representatives), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Barbara W. Weiss (Delegate), 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - William P. Whalen (State Senate), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Joe Wholey (Chair-Arlington County Board of Supervisors), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Mike White (Delegate), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Pamphlets. John M. Wilkins (Chair-Fairfax County Democratic Committee, Delegate, Eighth Congressional District Democratic Committee), 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Carrington Williams (Delegate, Lieutenant Governor, U.S. Senate), Undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Kenneth R. Wilson (Sheriff), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Frank Wolf (House of Representatives), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Bill Wrench (Chair-Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Tom Wright (Clerk of Court), 1975 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Gwenn Zoeckler (Eighth Congressional District Democratic Committee), Undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Elmo R. "Bud" Zumwalt (U.S. Senate), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Election - General, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Election - General, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Election - General, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Election - General, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Election - General, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Election - General, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Election - General, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Election - General, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Election - General, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Election - General, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Election - General, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Election - General, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Election - General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Election - General, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Election - General, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Election - General, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Election - General, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Election - General, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Election - General, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Election - General, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Election - General, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Election - General, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Election - Virginia, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Election - Virginia, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Election - Virginia, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Election - Virginia, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Election - Virginia, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Election - Virginia House of Delegates, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Election - Virginia House of Delegates, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Election - Virginia House of Delegates, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Election - Virginia House of Delegates, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Election - U.S. Senate, House of Representatives, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Election - U.S. Senate, House of Representatives, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Election - House of Representatives, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Election - House of Representatives, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Election - U.S. Senate, House of Representatives, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Election - U.S. Senate, House of Representatives, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Election - President, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Election - President, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Election - President, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Election - Democratic Party, Undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Election - Republican Party, Undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Election - Local Issues, Undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Series 2: Bumper stickers, 1965-2009
  - John W. Adams, Jr. (Delegate), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - F. Keith Adkinson (Delegate), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Joseph Alexander (Board of Supervisors), 1974-1979 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - George F. Allen (Governor), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Hunter B. Andrews (U.S. Senate), 1978 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Terry C. Armstrong (Sheriff), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Frederick A. Babson, Jr. (U.S. Senate), Undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Gerald L. Baliles (Attorney General), 1981 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Warren E. Barry (Delegate), Undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Bateman (Governor), Undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - William C. Battle (Governor), 1969 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Harry L. Bedsworth (Board of Supervisors), 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - James B. Boren (House of Representatives), 1986 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Adelard L. "Abe" Brault (State Senate), Undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - David C. Brickley (House of Representatives), 1988 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Joel T. Broyhill (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Dean E. Brundage (Delegate), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - John S. Buckley (Delegate), Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Jim Burch (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - John B. Burkel (Sheriff), Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (U.S. Senate), Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Leslie L. Byrne (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Mary F. Cahill (Delegate), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Vincent F. Callahan, Jr. (Delegate, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - A.J. "Joe" Canada, Jr. (Lieutenant Governor), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Warren I. Cikins (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - J. Marshall Coleman (Attorney General, Governor), Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Gerry Connolly (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Flora M. Crater (Delegate), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - John M. Dalton, Jr. (Governor), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Gilbert K. Davis (Commonwealth Attorney), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Richard J. Davis (Lieutenant Governor, U.S. Senate), 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Thomas M. Davis, III (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - H. Dunlop "Buz" Dawbarn (Lieutenant Governor), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - James H. Dillard, II (Delegate), Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Sandra L. Duckworth (Board of Supervisors), 1975-1983 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - William R. Durland (House of Representatives), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - William L. Durrer (Board of Supervisors), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Wyatt B. Durrette (Attorney General), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Clive L. Duval, II (U.S. Senate, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - M. Patton Echols, Jr. (Attorney General), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Gary P. Eklund (Delegate), 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Dudley J. "Buzz" Emick, Jr. (Lieutenant Governor), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Lester A. Fettig (Delegate), Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Joseph L. Fisher (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Howard E. Futch (Board of Supervisors), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Ray L. Garland (U.S. Senate), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Joseph V. Garlan, Jr. (State Senate), Undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - James Gilmore (Attorney General), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Mills Godwin (Governor), Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Virgil H. Goode, Jr. (U.S. Senate), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Robert E. Harris (Delegate), Undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Edythe C. Harrison (U.S. Senate), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Horace Henderson (U.S. Senate), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - John F. "Jack" Herrity (Chair-Board of Supervisors, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - M.J. "Mike" Hershman (Delegate), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Betsy W. Hinkle (Board of Supervisors), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Omer L. Hirst (State Senate), Undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Richard Hobson (Delegate), Undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Pat Holland (Alexandria Sheriff), Undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Jon D. Holstine (Board of Supervisors), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Linwood Holton (U.S. Senate), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - James Hoofnagle (Clerk of Court), Undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - William Hoofnagle (Chair-Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Robert F. Horan, Jr. (Commonwealth Attorney, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor), Undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Karetta B. Hubbard (Delegate), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Maya A. Huber (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - M. Wayne Huggins (Sheriff), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Charles E. Kaufman (Delegate), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Gladys B. Keating (Delegate), Undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Jane M. King (Delegate), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - David B. Kinney (House of Representatives), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Marilyn Klein (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Elaine A. Lailas (Delegate), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Edward E. Lane (Attorney General), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Charles B. Lankford (Sheriff), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Michael Patrick Leahy (Delegate), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Ira M. Lechner (Lieutenant Governor, House of Representatives), 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Alan H. Magazine (Board of Supervisors), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Conrad J. Marshall (Delegate), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Randolph J. May (Delegate), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Dorothy S. McDiarmid (Delegate), Undated (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Virginia E. McEnearney (Board of Supervisors), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Kyle E. McSlarrow (House of Representatives), 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Frank Medico (Delegate), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - John L. Melnick (Delegate, Attorney General), Undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Vernon H. Miles (Delegate), Undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Andrew P. Miller (Attorney General, Governor, U.S. Senate), 1969-1978 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Harold O. Miller (House of Representatives), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Audrey C. Moore (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Brian J. Moran (Governor), 2009 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - James P. Moran, Jr. (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Dennis Patrick "Pat" Mullins (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Robert J. Murrin (State Senate), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Oliver L. North (U.S. Senate), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Jerry W. Norton (Delegate), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Richard Dudley Obenshain (U.S. Senate), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Brendan P. O'Hara (Delegate), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Jean R. Packard (Chair-Board of Supervisors, State Senate), 1972-1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Stanford E. Parris (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Martha B. Pennino (House of Representatives), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Martin H. Perper (Delegate, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - G. Conoly Phillips (U.S. Senate), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Rufus C. Phillips, III (Board of Supervisors, House of Representatives, U.S. Senate), 1971-1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Owen B. Pickett (U.S. Senate), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Kenneth R. Plum (Delegate), Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Lawrence D. Pratt (Delegate), 1977-1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Joseph D. Ragan (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - George C. Rawlings, Jr. (Office Unidentified), Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Richard S. "Major" Reynolds (Lieutenant Governor), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Marie W. Ridder (Delegate), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - E. Stanley Rittenhouse (House of Representatives), 1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Charles S. Robb (Lieutenant Governor, Governor, U.S. Senate), Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Thomas Jefferson Rothrock (Delegate), Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Embry Cobb Rucker (Delegate), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Thomas D. Rust (State Senate), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Jim Sandy (Delegate), Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Richard L. Saslaw (State Senate, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Beverly J. Schwarz (Delegate), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - James M. Scott (Board of Supervisors), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - John L. Scott (State Senate), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - William L. Scott (U.S. Senate, House of Represenatatives), 1966-1976 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Jim Settle (Sheriff), Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - George P. Shafran (Lieutenant Governor), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Nancy L. Shands (Board of Supervisors), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Erwin S. "Shad" Solomon (Attorney General), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - William B. Spong, Jr. (U.S. Senate), 1966-1972 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Nora Anderson Squyres (Delegate), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Christopher Stokes (Sheriff), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Vernon LeRoy "Lee" Strang (Delegate), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - James R. Tate (House of Representatives, State Senate), 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - David L. Temple (Delegate), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - John M. Thoburn (Delegate, State Senate), Undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Marie B. Travesky (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Paul S. Trible, Jr. (U.S. Senate), 1982 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Drew Valentine (Delegate), Undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Raymond E. Vickery, Jr. (Delegate, House of Representatives), Undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Charles L. Waddell (State Senate), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - John W. Warner (U.S. Senate), Undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Mark R. Warner (Governor, U.S. Senate), 2001-2008 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - John B. Watkins, IV (State Senate), 1975-1979 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Patricia Watt (Chair-Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Vivian Watts (Delegate, Chair-Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Robert L. Weinberg (House of Representatives), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Barbara W. Weiss (Delegate), 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Carrington Williams (Delegate, U.S. Senate), Undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Kenneth R. Wilson (Sheriff), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Frank Wolf (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Admiral Elmo R. "Bud" Zumwalt, Jr. (U.S. Senate), 1976 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Election - General "Nixon-Scott", 1972 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Election - General "Carter - Zumwalt", 1976 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Election - General "Ford - Tate", 1976 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Election - General "Dukakis - Robb - Weinberg", 1988 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Election - Virginia "Virginia's future first: Godwin - Dalton - Echols", 1973 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Election - Virginia "Dalton - Canada - Coleman New energy for Virginia", 1977 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Election - Virginia "Howell - Robb - Lane", 1977 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Election - Virginia "Robb - Davis - Baliles", 1981 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Election - Virginia "Allen - Farris - Gilmore", 1993 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Election - President "Clinton - Gore", 1992 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Election - Democratic Party, Undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Election - Republican Party, Undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Election - Local Issues "Accountants: Deduct the Blue Laws!", Undated (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Election - Local Issues "Forward Fairfax", Undated (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Election - Local Issues "Pull for Librarians! Vote 'Yes'", Undated (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Election - Local Issues "Support Park Bonds", Undated (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Election - Local Issues "Virginia Bonds Yes", Undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Election - Local Issues "Vote Yes. Virginia's the Winner! [horse racing], Undated (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Election - Local Issues "Yes Parks in Fairfax County", Undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Series 3: Buttons, 1963-1994
  - F. Keith Adkinson (Delegate), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Joseph Alexander (Board of Supervisors), 1974-1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Terry C. Armstrong (Sheriff), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Frederick A. Babson, Jr. (Chair-Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Barry [?] (Office Unidentified) "My Barry Button", Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - William C. Battle (Governor), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Bob [?] (Office Unidentified) "I like Bob", Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Eddie Boone (Sheriff), Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Dean E. Brundage (Delegate), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - John S. Buckley (Delegate), Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (U.S. Senate) Cardinal logo, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (U.S. Senate) "Ask me why I'm for Byrd.", Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Cahill (Office Unidentified), Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Warren I. Cikins (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Gwendalyn F. Cody (Delegate), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Flora M. Crater (Delegate), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - John N. Dalton, Jr. (Governor) "I'm a Dalton Ringer", 1977 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gilbert K. Davis (Commonwealth Attorney), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Thomas M. Davis, III (House of Representatives), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Sandra L. Duckworth (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Clive L. Duval, II (House of Representatives) Envelope 1 of 2, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Clive L. Duval, II (House of Representatives) Envelope 2 of 2, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Gary P. Eklund (Delegate), Undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Carl Ericson (Board of Supervisors), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Lester A. Fettig (House of Representatives), Undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Joseph L. Fisher (House of Representatives) Envelope 1 of 2, Undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Joseph L. Fisher (House of Representatives) Envelope 2 of 2, Undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Garland (Office Unidentified), Undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives) Envelope 1 of 2, Undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives) Envelope 2 of 2, Undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives) "Return Herb Harris to Congress", Undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives) Labelled "1972 8th Dist. Cong. Primary Dem.", 1972 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - John F. "Jack" Herrity (Chair-Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Betsy W. Hinkle (Board of Supervisors), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Pat Holland (Alexandria Sheriff), Undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Hoofnagle (Office Unidentified), Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - William S. Hoofnagle (Chair-Board of Supervisors), 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Robert F. Horan, Jr. (Office Unidentified), Undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor) "This is the year for Henry Howell", Undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor) "I believe in Henry Howell", Undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor) "Henry Howell don't owe nothin to nobody.", Undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor) "I heard him talk. I'm for Howell.", Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor) "This year my vote goes to Henry Howell", Undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor) "Let's move Virginia ahead - Elect Howell Governor", Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor), Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor) "Henry Howell 1977 Governor's Club", 1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Karetta B. Hubbard (Delegate), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gerald W. Hyland (Delegate), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Charles E. Kaufman (Delegate), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Gladys B. Keating (Delegate), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Gladys B. Keating (Delegate), Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Edward Kennedy (President), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Edward E. Lane (Attorney General), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Charles B. Lankford (Sheriff), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Ira M. Lechner (Lieutenant Governor), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Ira M. Lechner (Lieutenant Governor) Shoeprint logo, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - John L. Melnick (Attorney General), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Miles (Delegate) "Miles for Delegate", Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Walter F. "Fritz" Mondale (President) "Virginia loves Grits & Fritz", 1984 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Stanford E. Parris (Office Unidentified), Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Rufus Phillips (House of Representatives), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Rufus Phillips (Board of Supervisors), Undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Rufus Phillips (U.S. Senate) "I'm stickin' with Rufus - 1978 Democratic Convention", 1978 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Kenneth R. Plum (Delegate) "A Democrat Working for You", 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Richard S. "Major" Reynolds (Lieutenant Governor), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Charles S. Robb (Governor) "Northern Virginia sends its best - Chuck Robb for Governor", 1981 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Tom Rust (State Senate), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Richard "Dick" L. Saslaw (House of Representatives), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Beverly J. Schwarz (Delegate), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Scott (Office Unidentified), Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - John L. Scott (Delegate), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - John L. Scott (State Senate), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Erwin S. "Shad" Solomon (Attorney General), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - William Spong (U.S. Senate), 1966-1972 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Nora Anderson Squyres (Delegate), 1982 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - David L. Temple (Delegate), 1982 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Robert Thoburn (House of Representatives), 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Marie Travesky (Board of Supervisors) "Marie's for me - Travesky for Supervisor", Undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - John B. Watkins, IV (State Senate), 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Karl Weickhardt (Delegate), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Barbara Weiss (Delegate), 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - John M. Wilkins (Delegate), 1972 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Election - Virginia "Democrats '77 Keating - Leahy - Rothrock - Saslaw - Strang", 1977 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Election - Virginia "Howell - Robb - Lane", 1977 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Election - Democratic Party "Vote Democratic", Undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Election - Local Issues "Vote YES School Bonds", Undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Series 4: Posters, 1966-1994
  - Joseph Alexander (Board of Supervisors), 1975
  - Gerald L. Baliles (Attorney General), 1981
  - Gerald L. Baliles (Attorney General) (2 copies), 1981
  - Gerald L. Baliles (Governor), 1985
  - James B. Boren (House of Representatives), 1986
  - David C. Brickley (House of Representatives), 1988
  - John S. Buckley (Delegate), Undated
  - Mary F. Cahill (Delegate), 1973
  - Vincent F. Callahan, Jr. (House of Representatives), 1976
  - J. Marshall Coleman, Undated
  - Flora M. Crater (Delegate), 1981
  - John N. Dalton, Jr. (Governor) (3 copies), 1977
  - John N. Dalton, Jr. (Governor) (3 copies), 1977
  - Richard J. Davis (Lieutenant Governor) (3 copies), 1981
  - Richard J. Davis (Lieutenant Governor), 1981
  - Richard J. Davis (Lieutenant Governor), 1981
  - Richard J. Davis (U.S. Senate), 1982
  - Richard J. Davis (U.S. Senate) (2 copies), 1982
  - Richard J. Davis, Undated
  - Sandra L. Duckworth (Board of Supervisors), Undated
  - Clive L. Duval, II (House of Representatives) (2 copies), 1966
  - Clive L. Duval, II (U.S. Senate), 1970